newvistalive.com 2015-03-22

# newvistalive - Privacy-Policy

This Privacy Statement describes the collection and use of personal data during your visit to our website and your use of the services of newvista. It also applies to any participation in prize draws or other competitions held by newvista itself.

For our other categories or services (e.g. advertising campaigns, communities, groups), further data protection information can be found in the respective FAQs as well as in the descriptions or conditions of the relevant service. 

The data protection provisions of external services (e.g. awards partners) or social networks (e.g. facebook, Google+, Pinterest, twitter, etc), which you may use during your visit to newvista, also apply.

Newvista takes the privacy of all personal information, however collected, very seriously.  We comply with the principles of the Data Protection Act 1998 and act in accordance with the Market Research Society Code of Conduct which can be found at www.mrs.org.uk/standards/codeconduct.htm.  The following information sets out our privacy policy and the measures we take to protect privacy and personal information.

All personally identifiable information provided to newvista through the completion of any survey is confidential and will not be given out to anyone.

All answers to survey questions are entirely anonymous and are only analysed along with all other respondent answers. Only anonymised, non-attributable data will be disclosed to clients or others for research purposes or for the promotion of services provided by newvista.

Data drawn from surveys may be reported by newspapers and / or other media organisations and may be displayed on the newvista website  www.newvistalive.com. In all cases, only anonymised, non-attributable data will be disclosed.  

All personal data is stored securely and is safeguarded under the 1998 Data Protection Act.

In common with other online polling organisations, newvista may use cookies.  A cookie is a text file placed in the browser directory of a computer’s hard drive.  Any website other than the one that set up the cookie cannot read the cookie.

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time.

###  **Facebook**

We use some services of the US social network, Facebook, on our platform. For example, we have installed the Facebook “Like button” (a so-called plug-in). That means we have integrated the “Like button” into our website using program code made available by Facebook.

Information is sent to Facebook at the point when a website is viewed, irrespective of whether the user clicks on the “Like button” or not. If the user clicks the “Like button”, Facebook then learns that the user likes the respective content. If the user is logged in to Facebook at the time, then he or she can be identified by Facebook (e.g. for advertising on Facebook). Facebook does not reveal in its current privacy policy precisely what information it collects and retains. We therefore recommend you refrain from using the “Like button” if you are unsure. 

Newvista also offers the function “Facebook Connect” so that you can register on or login at newvista using your Facebook login information. We assume that you protect your Facebook login information just as carefully as your newvista password. We do not receive the password which you use for your Facebook login as it is encrypted. 

If you are a Facebook member, but do not want Facebook to collect data about you through your newvista internet presence and connect it to your data saved on Facebook you must log out of Facebook before visiting newvista.  

###  Other plug-ins and external services 

Our website may also contain other so-called plug-ins. Each provider (e.g. Twitter) is responsible for its respective plug-in. We therefore, just as in the case of the Facebook plug-in, have no influence over the extent of data collected by the provider with the help of its plug-in or how the provider uses it. 

If you are not yet a customer of the provider of the plug-in or of the external service linked via the plug-in, i.e. you have not consented to its collecting or using data, we recommend you do not use or click on such plug-ins. 

If you are, however, already a user of the services linked via plug-in, you should find out about the type, scope and purposes of collection and use of personal information directly from the respective provider as well as about whether they process your information outside the EU.
